question_data = {
  "response_code": 0,
  "results": [
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Music",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "The music video to The Buggle&#039;s &quot;Video Killed the Radio Star&quot; was the first music video to broadcast on MTV.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Geography",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "San Marino is the only country completely surrounded by another country.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "History",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "The United States was a member of the League of Nations.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "In &quot;Sonic Adventure&quot;, you are able to transform into Super Sonic at will after completing the main story.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Geography",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Toronto is the capital city of the North American country of Canada.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "In Pok&eacute;mon, Ash&#039;s Pikachu refuses to go into a pokeball.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Geography",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "California is larger than Japan.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Film",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Brandon Routh plays the titular character in the movie &quot;John Wick&quot;.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Television",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Klingons express emotion in art through opera and poetry.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Activision created Battlefield 1.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    }
  ]
}